-I called about the apartment. You said--
-I know what I said. I know what you said.
(Past Sheldon:)I know what my mother said
on March 5th, 1992.
(Past Sheldon:)What is the sixth noble gas?
(Past Leonard:)-What?
-You said you're a scientist.
(Past Sheldon:)-What is the sixth noble gas?
-Uh, Radon?
(Past Sheldon:)Are you asking me or telling me?
(Past Leonard:)Telling you?
(Past Leonard:)Telling you.
(Past Sheldon:)All right. Next question.
(Past Sheldon:)Kirk or Picard?
(Past Leonard:)Oh, uh-- Well, that's tricky. Um--
Well, original series over
Next Generation, but Picard over Kirk.
(Past Sheldon:)Correct.
(Past Sheldon:)You've passed the first barrier
to roommatehood.
(Past Sheldon:)You may enter.
(Past Leonard(Enters apartment. It is bare except for two lawn chairs, a television and some whiteboards):)Oh, this is pretty nice.
(Past Leonard(Enters apartment. It is bare except for two lawn chairs, a television and some whiteboards):)-The bedrooms are back there?
-That depends.
(Past Leonard:)I don't understand.
Their existence is conditional?